

OBJECTIVE

As a game developer, I understand how mechanics can make or break the gameplay experience. As a designer and web developer, I know what a clean, responsive interface can do for your business. I enjoy technical aspects of design & development and polishing critical details that others may overlook. I am fully confident in proving what I say I can do. Contact me and let's work together.

EDUCATION

University of Richmond | Richmond, Virginia | 2019

Previously enrolled in the Coding Bootcamp managed by Trilogy Education Graduated on October 26th, 2019

- Studied full-stack web development (MERN Stack)
- Studied API integration and databasing (MongoDB/SQL)
- Studied command line interface and Git version-control on GitHub
- Created a web-based game called "Zone Unknown" for my final project

Longwood University | Farmville, Virginia | 2014 -2018

Majored in Graphic Design & Animation with a Bachelors of Fine Arts Graduated on May 19th, 2018

- Studied design elements, principles, visual problem solving, branding & production
- Studied 3D modeling, rigging, animation, texturing & rendering
- Created a realtime game in Unity called "TILT" for my senior project
- Member of LAS (Lancer Animation Studios) & the 3D Modeling Club

WORK EXPERIENCE

Target | Midlothian, Virginia | Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

Flexible Fulfillment

- Shopped for online orders and in-store pickups for arriving customers
- Packed and prepared orders for UPS transit

Kroger | Midlothian, Virginia | May 2016 - Feb 2017

Clicklist Attendant

- Shopped for online orders and prepared groceries for arriving customers
- Finalized customer payments car-side & loaded their groceries for them

SKILLS & CAPABILITIES

Game Development Pipeline (Unity/C#)
Full-Stack Web Development (MERN Stack)
API & Database Integration (AJAX/MongoDB/SQL)
Command Line Interface, Git Version-Control & Deployment
Vector Creation, Image Manipulation & Motion Graphics
3D Modeling, Rigging, Animation, Texturing & Rendering
Leadership, Teamwork & Logical Problem Solving



